A Guide to the Warren Weaver papers FA419
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Reprints, 1920-1987; 1933-1977; 12; 6 Cubic Feet
  - Works by Others, 2
    - Works by Others, 1958 (Box 59, Folder 504-505)
      - Jones, D.F.: The American Naturalist: Heterosis and Homeostasis in Evolution and in Applied Genetics, 1958 November-December (Box 59, Folder 504-505)
      - Kruskal, William H.: Journal of the American Statistical Association: Ordinal Measures of Association, 1958 December (Box 59, Folder 504-505)
      - Schinzel, A. and W. Sierpinski: ACTA Arithmetical IV: Sur Les Simmes de Quatre Cubes, 1958 (Box 59, Folder 504-505)
      - United Nations General Assembly: Report of the United Nations Scientific Committee of the Effects of Atomic Radiation, 1958 (Box 59, Folder 504-505)
    - Works by Others, 1959 (Box 60, Folder 506-507)
      - Szilard, Leo: Proceedings of the National Academy of Scienes: On the Nature of the Aging Process, 1959 January (Box 60, Folder 506-507)
      - Schmitt, Francis O.: Modern Physics: Molecular Biology and the Physical Basis of Life Processes, 1959 January (Box 60, Folder 506-507)
      - Von Bertalanffy, Ludwig: Bulletin of the Menniger Clinic: Some Biological Considerations on the Problem of Mental Illness, 1959 March (Box 60, Folder 506-507)
      - Goodman, Leo A. and William H. Kruskal: Journal of the American Statistical Association: Measures of Association for Cross Classifications, 1959 March (Box 60, Folder 506-507)
      - Shrader, James Houston. ed.: Religious Inquiry: Exploratory Studies on Emperic Approaches to Religion, 1959 April (Box 60, Folder 506-507)
      - Dunham, Charles L.: United States Atomic Energy Commission: Radioactive Fallout: A Two-Year Summary Report, 1959 May (Box 60, Folder 506-507)
      - Slichter, Louis B.: Mining Congress Journal: Mining Geophysics, 1959 May (Box 60, Folder 506-507)
      - National Association of Science Writers: Newsletter, 1959 June 1 (Box 60, Folder 506-507)
      - Potter, Robert D.: New York Medicine: Medicine and the Press, 1959 June 5 (Box 60, Folder 506-507)
      - Cook, J.W.: Nature: The Role of the Scholar in Society, 1959 June 27 (Box 60, Folder 506-507)
      - Kendrew, J.C.: Federation Proceedings: Structure and Function in Myoglobin and Other Proteins, 1959 July (Box 60, Folder 506-507)
      - Shrader, James Houston. ed.: Religious Inquiry: Exploratory Studies on Emperic Approaches to Religion, 1959 July (Box 60, Folder 506-507)
      - Pierce, J.R.: Science: Freedom in Research, 1959 September 4 (Box 60, Folder 506-507)
      - Committee on Religion and Science: The Satellite: Creation, Evolution and Darwin, 1959 Fall (Box 60, Folder 506-507)
      - United States Department of Health, Education and Welfare: Physicians for a Growing America, 1959 October (Box 60, Folder 506-507)
      - Platt, John R.: The Sweep and Excitement of Science, 1959 November 6 (Box 60, Folder 506-507)
      - Goodman, Leo A.: The American Journal of Sociology: Quantitative Methods for the Study of Identifiability, 1959 November (Box 60, Folder 506-507)
      - Hays, David G., E.K. Renner and D.V. Mohr: The Rand Corporation: Studies in Machine Translation 4: Manual for Pre-Editing Russian Scientific Texts (Revised: 1961 June 15), 1959 December 4 (Box 60, Folder 506-507)
      - Mcmullin, Ernan: America: Science and the Catholic Religion, 1959 December 12 (Box 60, Folder 506-507)
      - Goodman, Leo A.: Biometrika: Partial Tests for Partial Taus, 1959 December (Box 60, Folder 506-507)
      - Menger, K.: Mathematical Gazette: Gulliver in the Land without One, Two, Three, 1959 December (Box 60, Folder 506-507)
      - Kirk, John R.: The Centennial Review: Science and Faith, 1959 Winter (Box 60, Folder 506-507)
      - Bodo, G.: Proceedings of the Royal Society: The Crystal Structure of Myoglobin V. A low-resoultion three-dimensional Fourier synthesis of sperm-whale myglobin crystals, 1959 (Box 60, Folder 506-507)
      - DuBridge, L.A., and Paul Epstein.: Biographical Memoirs: Robert Andrews Millikan, 1959 (Box 60, Folder 506-507)
      - Huxley, J.S.: Collins: Introduction to the Phenomenon of Man, 1959 (Box 60, Folder 506-507)
      - Journal of Molecular Biology: Chemical and Crystallographic Study of the Two Fractions of Adult Horse Hemoglobin, 1959 (Box 60, Folder 506-507)
      - National Academy of Sciences: A Commentary on the Report of the United Nations Scientific Committee on the Effects of Atomic Radiation, 1959 (Box 60, Folder 506-507)
      - Williams, Roger J.: Why Human Genetics?, 1959 (Box 60, Folder 506-507)
    - Works by Others, 1960 (Box 60, Folder 508-509)
      - Bragg, Sir Lawrence: The Listener: Popularizing Science on Television, 1960 January 14 (Box 60, Folder 508-509)
      - Neurath, Hans: Archives of Biochemistry and Biophysics: Kaj Ulrik Linderstrom-Lang, 1960 January (Box 60, Folder 508-509)
      - Swann, W.F.G.: American Journal of Physics: Certain Matters in Relation to the Restricted Theory of Relativity, with Special Reference to the Clock Paradox and the Paradox of the Identical Twins, 1960 January (Box 60, Folder 508-509)
      - Potter, Robert D.: New York Medicine: The Impact of Medical Reporting on the Public, 1960 February 5 (Box 60, Folder 508-509)
      - Kendrew, J.C., R.E. Dickerson, B.E. Strandberg, R.G. Hart and D.R. Davies: Nature: Structure of the Myglobin, 1960 February 13 (Box 60, Folder 508-509)
      - Kendrew, J.C.: The New Scientist: The Structures of Haemoglobin and Myoglobin, 1960 February 25 (Box 60, Folder 508-509)
      - Kruskal, William H.: Technometrics: Some Remarks on Wild Observations, 1960 February (Box 60, Folder 508-509)
      - Blackett, P.M.S.: Nature: Tizard and the Science of War, 1960 March 5 (Box 60, Folder 508-509)
      - Szilard, Leo: Proceedings of the National Academy of Scienes: The Molecular Basis of Antibody Formation, 1960 March (Box 60, Folder 508-509)
      - United States Atomic Energy Commission: What's Available in the Atomic Energy Literature?, 1960 March (Box 60, Folder 508-509)
      - Holton, Gerard: Science: Modern Science and the Intellectual Tradition, 1960 April 22 (Box 60, Folder 508-509)
      - Szilard, Leo: Proceedings of the National Academy of Scienes: The Control of the Formation of Specific Proteins in Bacteria and in Animal Cells, 1960 May (Box 60, Folder 508-509)
      - Kruskal, William H.: AAUP Bulletin: Faculty Size, Minimum Salaries, and Committee Z (and Follow-Up), 1960 Summer (Box 60, Folder 508-509)
      - Research Laboratory Bulletin, 1960 Summer (Box 60, Folder 508-509)
      - Harper, K.E., D.G. Hayes and B.J. Scott: The Rand Corporation: Studies in Machine Translation 8: Manual for Post-Editing Russian Text, 1960 July 15 (Box 60, Folder 508-509)
      - Huxley, J.S.: The Humanist: Science and Human Values, 1960 August (Box 60, Folder 508-509)
      - Morison, Robert S.: Christianity and Crisis: Darwinism: Foundation for an Ethical System?, 1960 August 8 (Box 60, Folder 508-509)
      - Hays, David G.: The Rand Corporation: Grouping and Dependency Theories, 1960 September 8 (Box 60, Folder 508-509)
      - National Association of Science Writers: Newsletter, 1960 September (Box 60, Folder 508-509)
      - Science and Freedom: A Bulletin of the Committee on Science and Freedom: Freedom and Efficieny, 1960 October (Box 60, Folder 508-509)
      - Williams, J.D.: Rand Corporation: Toward Intelligent Machines, 1960 December 29 (Box 60, Folder 508-509)
      - Gaffron, Hans: Perspectives in Biology and Medicine: The Origin of Life, 1960 Winter (Box 60, Folder 508-509)
      - Science and Freedom: A Bulletin of the Committee on Science and Freedom, 1960 December (Box 60, Folder 508-509)
      - Thompson, George: Society for Freedom in Science: The Two Aspects of Science, 1960 December (Box 60, Folder 508-509)
      - Light, Israel: Journalism Quaterly: Science Writing: Status and Needs, 1960 Winter (Box 60, Folder 508-509)
      - Garfield, Eugene ed.: Institute for Information: Index Chemiscus, 1960 (Box 60, Folder 508-509)
      - Institute for Scientific Information: Index Chemiscus, 1960 (Box 60, Folder 508-509)
      - Jeffries, Zay: Biographical Memoirs: Charles Franklin Kettering, 1960 (Box 60, Folder 508-509)
      - Huxley, J.S.: The University of Chicago Centennial: Evolution After Darwin, 1960 (Box 60, Folder 508-509)
      - Meehan, John: Science News Workshop: Through the Language Barrier, 1960 (Box 60, Folder 508-509)
      - Tribus, Myron: Journal of Applied Mechanics: Information Theory as the Basis for Thermostatics and Thermodynamics, 1960 (Box 60, Folder 508-509)
    - Works by Others, 1961 (Box 60, Folder 510)
      - American Institute of Physics: Glossary of Terms Frequently Used in Optics and Spectroscopy, 1961 March 1 (Box 60, Folder 510)
      - Bonner, James: The Saturday Evening Post: The Message of Life, 1961 April 15 (Box 60, Folder 510)
      - Goldstein, H.H.: Science: Information Theory, 1961 May 5 (Box 60, Folder 510)
      - Astbury, W.T.: Nature: Molecular Biology or Ultrastructural Biology, 1961 June 17 (Box 60, Folder 510)
      - The Key Reporter, 1961 Summer (Box 60, Folder 510)
      - Kusch, Polykarp: The Key Reporter: Scientists and Laymen, 1961 Summer (Box 60, Folder 510)
      - Wigner, Eugene P.: The Unreasonable Effectiveness of Mathematics in the Natural Sciences, 1961 July 7 (Box 60, Folder 510)
      - Science of Mind, 1961 July (Box 60, Folder 510)
      - Shamos, Morris H.: Saturday Review: Science for Citizens, 1961 September 15 (Box 60, Folder 510)
      - Research Laboratory Bulletin, 1961 Fall (Box 60, Folder 510)
      - Huxley, J.S.: Perspective: The Coming New Religion of Humanism, 1961 October (Box 60, Folder 510)
      - Sherburne, E.G.: American Association for the Advancement of Science: An Evaluation of Television Film, 1961 November (Box 60, Folder 510)
      - Box, G.E.P., and G.C. Tiao: University of Wisconsin: A Further Look at Robustness via Bayes' Theorem, 1961 December (Box 60, Folder 510)
      - National Academy of Sciences: Effects of Inhaled Radioactive Particles, 1961 (Box 60, Folder 510)
      - National Academy of Sciences: Effects of Ionizing Radiation on the Human Hemopoietic System, 1961 (Box 60, Folder 510)
      - National Academy of Sciences: Long Term Effects of Ionizing Radiations from External Sources, 1961 (Box 60, Folder 510)
    - Works by Others, 1961 (Box 61, Folder 511)
      - American Institute of Physics: Glossary of Terms Frequently Used in Optics and Spectroscopy, 1961 March 1 (Box 61, Folder 511)
      - Bonner, James: The Saturday Evening Post: The Message of Life, 1961 April 15 (Box 61, Folder 511)
      - Goldstein, H.H.: Science: Information Theory, 1961 May 5 (Box 61, Folder 511)
      - Astbury, W.T.: Nature: Molecular Biology or Ultrastructural Biology", 1973 January 8 (Box 61, Folder 511)
      - The Key Reporter, 1961 Summer (Box 61, Folder 511)
      - Kusch, Polykarp: The Key Reporter: Scientists and Laymen, 1961 Summer (Box 61, Folder 511)
      - Wigner, Eugene P.: The Unreasonable Effectiveness of Mathematics in the Natural Sciences, 1961 July 7 (Box 61, Folder 511)
      - Science of Mind, 1961 July (Box 61, Folder 511)
      - Shamos, Morris H.: Saturday Review: Science for Citizens, 1961 September 15 (Box 61, Folder 511)
      - Research Laboratory Bulletin, 1961 Fall (Box 61, Folder 511)
      - Huxley, J.S.: Perspective: The Coming New Religion of Humanism, 1961 October (Box 61, Folder 511)
      - Sherburne, E.G.: American Association for the Advancement of Science: An Evaluation of Television Film, 1961 November (Box 61, Folder 511)
      - Box, G.E.P., and G.C. Tiao: University of Wisconsin: A Further Look at Robustness via Bayes' Theorem, 1961 December (Box 61, Folder 511)
      - National Academy of Sciences: Effects of Inhaled Radioactive Particles, 1961 (Box 61, Folder 511)
      - National Academy of Sciences: Effects of Ionizing Radiation on the Human Hemopoietic System, 1961 (Box 61, Folder 511)
      - National Academy of Sciences: Long Term Effects of Ionizing Radiations from External Sources, 1961 (Box 61, Folder 511)
    - Works by Others, 1962 (Box 61, Folder 512)
      - Clarke, Leonard W.: Nature: Science in the Bible, 1962 January 6 (Box 61, Folder 512)
      - Lonsdale, Kathleen: Nature: Science and Ethics, 1962 January 20 (Box 61, Folder 512)
      - Huxley, J.S.: New Scientist: His Faith in Human Possibilities, 1962 January (Box 61, Folder 512)
      - Potter, Van R.: Land Economics: Bridge to the Future: The Concept of Human Progress, 1974 May 29-30 (Box 61, Folder 512)
      - Fox, Phyllis: American Institute of Physics: Glossary of Terms Frequently Used in Physics and Computers, 1962 May 22 (Box 61, Folder 512)
      - Wheeler, John A.: University (A Princeton Magazine): Relativity Today, 1962 Fall (Box 61, Folder 512)
      - Research Laboratory Bulletin, 1962 Fall (Box 61, Folder 512)
      - Huxley, J.S.: Perspectives in Biology and Medicine: Book Review of Dobzhansky's Mankind Evolving, 1962 Autumn (Box 61, Folder 512)
      - Simon, Herbert A.: Proceedings of the American Philosophical Society: The Architecture of Complexity, 1962 December (Box 61, Folder 512)
      - Commoner, Barry: Horizons in Biochemistry: Is DNA a Self-Duplicating Molecule?, 1962 (Box 61, Folder 512)
      - Hayek, F.A.: History and Theory: Communication, 1962 (Box 61, Folder 512)
    - Works by Others, 1973-1975 (Box 61, Folder 513)
      - Academy Reporter: Academy of Religion and Mental Health, 1963 February 100 (Box 61, Folder 513)
      - Usmani, I.H.: Science for Survival, 1963 March 19 (Box 61, Folder 513)
      - Piel, Gerard: Scientific American: The Acceleration of History, 1963 April 27 (Box 61, Folder 513)
      - Research Laboratory Bulletin, 1963 Summer (Box 61, Folder 513)
      - National Academy of Sciences: IQ Bulletin, 1963 July (Box 61, Folder 513)
      - Cassidy, Harold G.: American Scientist: The Muse and the Axiom, 1963 September (Box 61, Folder 513)
      - Nuclear Information: War and the Living Environment, 1974 June (Box 61, Folder 513)
      - Sherburne, E.G.: The Science Teacher: Future Citizens of A Scientific Democracy, 1963 November (Box 61, Folder 513)
      - Huxley, J.S.: Perspectives in Biology and Medicine: Eugenics in Evolutionary Perspective, 1963 Winter (Box 61, Folder 513)
      - Research Laboratory Bulletin, 1963/ 1964 Winter (Box 61, Folder 513)
      - Hayek, F.A.: Proceedings of the British Academy: Rules, Perception and Intelligibility, 1963 (Box 61, Folder 513)
      - National Academy of Sciences: The Behavior of Radioactive Fallout in Soils and Plants, 1963 (Box 61, Folder 513)
      - Potter, Van R.: National Cancer Institute Monograph: Models as Aids to Communication, 1963 (Box 61, Folder 513)
      - Ubell, Earl: American Cancer Society: Cancer: Research and Results, 1963 (Box 61, Folder 513)
      - Wheeler, John A.: Academic Press Inc.: Absence of a Gravitational Analog to Electrical Charges, 1963 (Box 61, Folder 513)
      - Wheeler, John A.and D.R. Brill: Sonderdruck Aus Physikalische Blatter Heft 8: Krummung der leeren Raum-Zeit als das Baumeterial der physikalischen Welt: Eine Einschatzung, 1963 (Box 61, Folder 513)
      - Wheeler, John A.: Philosophy of Science: Science and Survival, 1963 (Box 61, Folder 513)
    - Works by Others, 1964 (Box 61, Folder 514)
      - Coffin, Tristram: Holiday: Leo Szilard: The Conscience of a Scientist, 1964 February (Box 61, Folder 514)
      - Current, 1964 February (Box 61, Folder 514)
      - Slichter, Louis B.: Detection of a Signal of Limited Duration in the Presence of Noise, 1964 May 28 (Box 61, Folder 514)
      - Research Laboratory Bulletin, 1964 Summer (Box 61, Folder 514)
      - Potter, Van R.: Cancer Research: Biochemical Perspectives in Cancer Research, 1964 August (Box 61, Folder 514)
      - Gruenberger, Fred J.: Science: A Measure for Crackpots, 1964 September 25 (Box 61, Folder 514)
      - Science Fortnightly: Theory of DNA in Heredity is Modified, 1964 September 30 (Box 61, Folder 514)
      - Potter, Van R.: Science: Society and Science, 1964 November 20 (Box 61, Folder 514)
      - Dulbecco, Renato: Journal of the American Medical Association: Transformation of Cells in Vitro by DNA-Containing Viruses, 1964 November 23 (Box 61, Folder 514)
      - Memorial Service: John Davis Williams, 1964 December 6 (Box 61, Folder 514)
      - Beadle, George W.: Encyclopedia Britannica: The New Genetics, 1964 (Box 61, Folder 514)
      - Bendich, Aaron: Encyclopedia Americana: Nucleic Acid, 1974 December (Box 61, Folder 514)
    - Works by Others, 1965-1966 (Box 61, Folder 515)
      - Helmer, Olaf: The Rand Corporation: Social Technology, 1965 February (Box 61, Folder 515)
      - Potter, Van R.: The Nation: Council on the Future, 1965 February 8 (Box 61, Folder 515)
      - Cohen, H. and S.I. Rubinow: System Theory: Some Mathematical Topics in Biology, 1974 December (Box 61, Folder 515)
      - Dulbecco, Renato: American Journal of Medicine: Characteristics of Virus-Cell Complexes, 1965 May (Box 61, Folder 515)
      - Research Laboratory Bulletin, 1965 Summer (Box 61, Folder 515)
      - Ingle, Dwight J.: The Pharos of Alpha Omega Alpha: Living Philosophy: Evolution as a Parameter of Existence, 1965 October (Box 61, Folder 515)
      - Kruskal, William H.: The Centennial Review: Statistics, Moliere and Henry Adams, 1965 Winter (Box 61, Folder 515)
      - Rosenblith, Walter A. and Norbert Wiener: The Journal of Nervous and Mental Disease: Norbert Wiener, 1965 (Box 61, Folder 515)
      - Stumpf, Samuel Enoch: Annuls of Internal Medicine: Some Moral Dimensions of Medicine, 1966 February (Box 61, Folder 515)
      - Chicago Today. The University of Chicago, 1966 Spring (Box 61, Folder 515)
      - Townes, Charles H.: The Technology Review: The Convergence of Science and Religion, 1966 May (Box 61, Folder 515)
      - Hearings Before the Subcomittee on Government Research of the Committee on Government Operations (United States Senate). United States Government Printing Office: Equitable Distribution of R&D Funds by Government Agencies, 1966 July 25-27 (Box 61, Folder 515)
      - Hartley, Sir Harold: Proceedings of the Royal Society: John Dalton, F.R.S. (1766-1844) and the Atomic Theory: A Lecture to Commemorate his Bicentary, 1966 November 10 (Box 61, Folder 515)
      - Manglesdorpf, Paul C.: The American Philosophical Society: Henry Agard Wallace, 1966 (Box 61, Folder 515)
    - Works by Others, 1967 (Box 62, Folder 516)
      - Morgan, Karl Z.: Presented at St. John's Lutheran Church, Knoxville, TN: Conflict Between Science and Religion, 1967 January 29 (Box 62, Folder 516)
      - Jacobson, Cecil B. and Valerie L. Magyar: AAUW Journal: Toward a Better Tomorrow, 1967 January (Box 62, Folder 516)
      - Riddle, Oscar: Zygon (Journal of Religion and Science): The Emergenge of Good and Evil, 1967 March (Box 62, Folder 516)
      - Scientist and Citizen, 1975 May (Box 62, Folder 516)
      - Scientist and Citizen, 1967 August / September (Box 62, Folder 516)
      - Medical Affairs: Moral Issues Relating to the Use of Humans and Animals in Research, 1967 September (Box 62, Folder 516)
      - Piel, Gerard: The Common Sense of Mr. Conant, 1967 October 24 (Box 62, Folder 516)
      - Scientist and Citizen, 1967 October (Box 62, Folder 516)
      - Hearings Before the Subcomittee on Government Research of the Committee on Government Operations (United States Senate). United States Government Printing Office: An Inventory of Congressional Concern with Research and Development, 1967 October 11 (Box 62, Folder 516)
      - Brooks, Harvey: Problem of Science Policy: Seminar at Jouy-en Josas on Science: Can Science be Planned?, 1967 (Box 62, Folder 516)
    - Works by Others, 1968 (Box 62, Folder 517-518)
      - Science Policy Bulletin, 1975 May (Box 62, Folder 517-518)
      - Weinberg, Alvin M.: Social Stress, Think Tanks, and Unviersities (Revised: 1969 January 30), 1968 March 4 (Box 62, Folder 517-518)
      - Burr, George L.: As I See It, 1968 March 27 (Box 62, Folder 517-518)
      - Fox, William T.R.: International Studies Quarterly: Science, Technology and International Politics, 1968 March (Box 62, Folder 517-518)
      - Scientist and Citizen, 1968 April (Box 62, Folder 517-518)
      - Scientist and Citizen, 1968 June/July (Box 62, Folder 517-518)
      - Scientist and Citizen, 1968 August (Box 62, Folder 517-518)
      - Scientist and Citizen, 1968 September (Box 62, Folder 517-518)
      - Weinberg, Alvin M.: Minerva: A Review of Science, Learning, and Policy: Scientific Choice and the Scientific Muchrakers: Review Article, 1968-1969 Autumn-Winter (Box 62, Folder 517-518)
      - Scientist and Citizen, 1968 October (Box 62, Folder 517-518)
      - National Academy of Sciences: The Mathematial Sciences: A Report, 1968 November 22 (Box 62, Folder 517-518)
      - National Science Foundation: Federal Funds for Research, Development, and Other Scientific Activities, 1968 (Box 62, Folder 517-518)
    - Works by Others, 1969-1972 (Box 62, Folder 519)
      - Seaborg, Glenn: U.S. Atomic Energy Commission: The Place of Values in a World of Facts, 1969 September 17 (Box 62, Folder 519)
      - Monod, Jacques: The Salk Institute: From Biology to Ethics, 1969 October (Box 62, Folder 519)
      - Hirsch, Jerry: Seminars in Psychiatry: Behavior: Genetic Analysis and Its Biosocial Consequences, 1970 February (Box 62, Folder 519)
      - Bronowski, J.: Synthese: New Concepts in the Evolution of Complexity, 1970 (Box 62, Folder 519)
      - Longuet-Higgins, H.C., D.J. Willshaw and O.P. Buneman: Quaterly Review of Biophysics: Theories of Associative Recall, 1970 (Box 62, Folder 519)
      - Salk, Jonas: Basil O'Conner, 1972 March 13 (Box 62, Folder 519)
      - Wallis, W. Allen: Leonard Jimmie Savage, 1972 March (Box 62, Folder 519)
      - Sherburne, E.G.: Problems, Publics, and Stages of Development in Public Understanding of Science, 1972 November 29-39 (Box 62, Folder 519)
      - Harrar, J. George: Year Book of the American Philosophical Society: Raymond Blaine Fosdick, 1972 (Box 62, Folder 519)
    - Works by Others, 1973-1987 (Box 63, Folder 520)
      - Harvard University: Program on Public Conceptions of Science, 1973 January (Box 63, Folder 520)
      - Flanders, Harley: The American Mathematical Monthly: The Mathematical Association of America, 1975 Fall (Box 63, Folder 520)
      - Harvard University: Program on Public Conceptions of Science, 1973 October (Box 63, Folder 520)
      - American Philosophical Society: Symposium on Copernicus, 1973 December 31 (Box 63, Folder 520)
      - National Academy of Sciences: Science and Technology in Presidential Policy Making, 1974 June (Box 63, Folder 520)
      - McConnell, R.A.: ESP and the Physics of the Next Decades, 1975 February (Box 63, Folder 520)
      - McConnell, R.A.: An Evidential Bibliography of Parapsychology, 1975 (Box 63, Folder 520)
      - McConnell, R.A.: A Sociological Bibliography of Parapsychology, 1975 (Box 63, Folder 520)
      - Present, Gerald (ed.): American Institute of Physics: Physics News in 1977 (Box 63, Folder 520)
      - J. George Harrar: Year Book of the American Philosophical Society: Warren Weaver, 1979 (Box 63, Folder 520)
      - Rees, Mina: Biographical Memoirs: Warren Weaver, 1987 (Box 63, Folder 520)
    - Works by Others, undated (Box 63, Folder 521)
      - Life: DNA's Code: Key to All Life (Box 63, Folder 521)
      - Johnson, D. Gale: The Conquest of Hunger (Box 63, Folder 521)
      - Holter, H.: Comptes Rendus Des Travaux du Laboratoire Carlsberg: K.U. Liderstrom-Lang (Box 63, Folder 521)
      - Kusch, Polykarp: Unpublished (1960s): The Interdependence of Science and the Mass Media (Box 63, Folder 521)
      - Maugh, Thomas H.: American Association for the Advancement of Science: Energy: A Glossary (Box 63, Folder 521)